<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kangaroo</title>
    <link>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kangaroo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Apache 2.0</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kangaroo-server.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>API Basics</title>
      <link>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/basics/</guid>
      <description>Required Headers Every request made against the administration API requires the following headers:
 Authorization: This header is required for all protected resources, and should contain the bearer token. For example: Authorization: Bearer my_granted_access_token. X-Requested-By: This header needs to be sent with every request, in order to guard against CSRF attacks. The content may be anything, we recommend you use some human-readable string that identifies your application. Accept: This header should be set to application/json.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Project</title>
      <link>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Contributing We maintain an active list of issues, and use github&amp;rsquo;s project tracker for larger bodies of work. To coordinate and ensure that your work is not being duplicated, please reach out the the community in the IRC Channel.
Philosophy The project adheres to several philosophies that impact our design decisions and architecture.
Secure by Default In order to encourage a safe and secure internet, the project will default to the most secure configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authorization API</title>
      <link>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/authz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/authz/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kangaroo</title>
      <link>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/</guid>
      <description>Kangaroo is an open source, multi-tenant, OAuth2 Authorization server. It fully supports RFC 6749 (The original OAuth2 Specification), and aspires to be a reference implementation thereof. We intend to expand the scope of this project to include other OAuth2 related RFC&amp;rsquo;s.
docker run -it -p 8080:8080 krotscheck/kangaroo-authz:latest  The above command will start a standalone server at https://localhost:8080/. This server will sign its own SSL certificate on startup; Your browser will notify you of the untrusted nature of this certificate, every time the process is restarted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OAuth2</title>
      <link>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/oauth2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kangaroo-server.github.io/oauth2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>